I.
Just.
Wore.
All. I want to get that morning
when I left to be on account of the man
that they marched out of the right on this
level but we we have the C.I. D.
It's left even less about my plan that
kept us awake with all the same night.
That's why one surprise when the commissioner
asked is up the conference room for
a bit of
a top talk to us plenty we knew that it
didn't help and I don't know what was ahead
up.
Nicely had that when the local breaks Oh
shut it if you want to keep up enough of
the temp up without having already
passed down the back of my.
That one the commissioner. Healthy in.
The city both you. Gentlemen if you wish
to know what able men you are reading any
of the works of popular fiction but dammit
I join achievements but don't I think of
you read the daily paper. They might
give you an inferiority complex.
I hate to make you. But
they're confronted with
a series of the most atrocious another
since Jack the Ripper. And in the meantime
the sea ID might as well be playing at
a flea all the good we've
accomplished all of.
That and him. He took the red flags
and into the city stands for
a woman brutally murdered tell us
a woman is dead and. These are no ordinary
crimes these are the worst I've seen who
kills first unusual after a brutal act of
a part of his victim's body and carries it
away with him as loathsome single me out
of his cherry tree when it's not so
and you haven't turned in one clue
you haven't given me one lead here you
sit and wait on you the whole thing came
with your.
Well no it had along the way it was down
Lambert what a young woman with owning
a home like last night
saw some stuff. It was
a constable he spoke to her on
the walk along with Justin K.
. Michelle on the lam the stairway to
the basement lodging where she lives.
I can honestly Miles what
happened after that.
The of.
My pride in my pocket and went to see
the manager so I helped out Inspector
starving myself in the past Mr Sharp Oh.
If ever
a man needed help I. Think
for a second. For the senses women
here and I have none and everyone with
a right forefinger hacked off not
hacked but the great. Cleanly
expertly severed. The skilled surgeon that's
around it too much about the age of my
sister. Is there no way of
stopping this Mr Holmes said.
There's
a way somehow. The does I promise I
promise nothing to go on that's the rough
part of it I can get far without knowing
the motive you know what the motives were
not the robbery of passion thanks to you
know yet then they all came
a totally unrelated family is that
it's like I said. Sorry Holmes I don't
I have wanted to blow can look at them so
the loose the bullet thing like that as
a token on the to the drink.
Limits that was given to this is that if
they did it doubles my friends and that to
banks because I'd run out of these never
to give and this thing Mr Holmes was
a pleasure to be of help stuff we got these
things out of my line again from maniac
you know this just for the
fun of the ad. Says to get
a human thing to. Fall cases.
And that's
a risk you have to stop
in to security. Applause
Oh no he's just a man. Have to
this method is madness. It's
a two faced as this it seems. Like it just
doing this channeling my from the pen.
I think you. Think it
was that you you think.
The judge when it left yes that is
daughter within. The BE SO NICE inspector.
You know everyone. Well. We got you
a week after.
I collect these things have
a great. Time ago if. I
Ever Get a mission. In
a very handsome one. On one purpose to be
an excellent imitation would you like to
come back that the next not play idea.
What it wishes take is judge
when it will be so nice.
That it
.
Good enough and not just no one thank you.
Things can and when you're not yes no I say
you don't mean that to grandma and you
can yes ma'am that you wouldn't
believe the things that
a. Child I like reading.
This one. You know. By my question.
I don't mind anything really except that
being with you now you really don't want
to believe it is not too seriously good
we're both quite grown up and quite.
You know Jessica.
And you know it's not.
Absent from us laughing. In
any light to be. And that to.
Happen I do.
Is when he wouldn't believe
it but he's a bit of
a man she loves the music and
she thinks that we will do.
To the best. We'll need to. I
can tune to. Play with until God.
And so that's why you talk about them
I think. Anything I could put them
in. Any
type of getting into never never. Land.
Isn't to have alleged. Suspects right.
Thank God willing to.
Going to testify that was
there yes I can tell by the
feel of this rather than about
a committed treason I might have allowed
it but the other side of that doctor was
a step further than that it only I could
find and what. One thing is unfortunate
victims have in common that Michael has
a motive. And must be something that Jack
the rest of us mere homicidal maniac that
was in the case of Jack the Ripper there
was one thing in common is the cameras
were all from one walk of life living in
the same technique the city in this case
and I grant you that his victims from all
walks of life and from different sections
of the city nobody thought
of this is not the work of
a homicidal maniac it's something infinitely
most sinister Miller creeps talking
about but. I'm convinced that these murders
are only incident of some larger and
more diabolical scheme maybe that where
the seven think is the answer to that
question my dear fellow that only hope of
solving these mysteries Yes Sister I'm so
happy has to love the holidays bright with
you and help and I'm looking forward to
being with you again on
new thing for the race is
a lump in your first i can picture sitting
here happily writing this letter and
that they're realizing that you
shot again when death. Hello Greg.
Or they want to hold our own for you
although I have my own Edgware Road I have
another one. There I
felt like I could after
a. Oh
my.
God not. On the side.
There's been another. Yes
no. I really don't feel
quite safe here myself.
Quite
a good one I don't much time
I see how I wish it. Did
yes. I don't know you have to help
me you've got to help but I don't
understand. I woke up a few minutes ago in
a body house of Edgware Road I don't know
how I came that I don't know when the
last thing I remember being here with
you. When I leave here well it was about.
It was ten forty five
because you seem to give
me. Detached not interested I
thought I said something to
offend I don't remember.
I can. Tell me as it happened.
Well the research thing is unusual.
It was ten forty five when I left.
Nine this morning when I
work over ten hours last
ten hours I can't account for and in my
pocket when I work I found an i Phone.
And. You can pick.
The man asking to see the gentleman
standing away. No no no no no peace I
see him
well delightful room not much like
a place to wake up in this
morning. Followed me here yet
I'll take you don't know. Quite the
contrary don't be afraid to George
you know my name oh yes
a very old and highly honored name and being
the bad of such a name and I was that
a wealthy man I thought you might
catch the debts yourself its price.
Rather than it has fallen into the hands
of the police. Is your time not take
initials. That you get.
It came out of. My side fold to haven't.
You any bidding bending over something. Of
a knife. When you put
something in your pocket.
Come along come allows a lot
of the motels with the missing
a treat not just talk
about what you just did.
You in your place but then tell me
all about this is the right thing
right happened to me you realize that
a day off all day and night dives is the
best you apparently as well rode much in
the dark that I.
I'll be going to climb to make them
a match they can. Practice
their tech.
Next moment of crisis from a great
emotion you know less than winning in
a club stuck in a mission
and many factions input
a total of concur to another
something and then thank you want to show
me make sure that this match address
getting this size not in
style. Come any time.
An amendment is an.
Interesting well if it can
have anything to have
one one of the him. That.
I was to know as wasn't.
Young lady said most
action I could come it could I to me.
Yes this is my conduct about you.
Excuse me please but when you sit down
and come up to me I think
it's quite alright.
That. I can tell yourself just
like you expect you know my name
now magic I show you I wasn't in your picture
the other doesn't the judge said you
can't you. It's about my father right. What
about your problem is that I don't know
what to do he's always been the
nice person. And he says nothing.
You know so I didn't think anything of it
when he was when you night before last
but he didn't come home to us to take the
time to come in to dinner to just paced
up and down in my brain hour after hour and
thank him for that we had but he wasn't
ready. To take a time. I couldn't sleep
a wink last night and I started hearing
things getting into what sort of thing
I had someone in the God meant to be my
friend. Then I could think of moving down
the garden path and I recognize my
father did encourage him God like if.
He had a spade in his
hand and he stopped at
a greenhouse three started to
dig this morning at daybreak
I I still long for God and found that
I think he would think that we have company
I was about to happen to get hold of
Inspector Greg didn't tell him to me just
once George the next time Kingston. That
was coming out quick.
Was not going to live
in it thank you would be in my way when
you come and he say thank you I got your
message yesterday. That Michael and.
Then. The son.
Of Mine did you think you know.
What's going on come on I don't know
like I was saying and then
I sleep OK along with.
They had an. Idea maybe with after
that to signal the ribs but it turned
out to play penetrated the hut because
a part of my family killed. Afraid of this
but the main thing to remember the man
in the cabin of the Senate big screen he
don't think he had anything to do I think
it's reasonable to assume that he just
thought someone that I've been simple George
is obviously been made it keep him from
telling me what I knew of the revenue was
small caliber Well the point blank range
was that I came into those French windows
the mud from the got me brought into the
boot joint not to surprise the into the.
The room through. All of the contests
but for the location of the wound
I say that he tended back for
a moment and at the time. I was with all
the space between his ribs and one muscle
chopped side you mean to say kept on going
even after he was shot no doubt about it
with that kind of blood just at
the desk. Something to offer.
Some. I don't know he was trying to tell
me helpful chap I don't think so much as
the belt over the top they know you'll
notice from the train the blood said George
made straight to the desk. Something
he was desperately anxious to get
although the right hands clenched That's
his actual get back into the left hand
eyes open. Finally one hand tension that
I'm going to be the right hand then hit is
the desk please note that George took
something off this desk something so
important that he studies
a lot of stuff of blood to get
it I want to know what it is.
I think the norm in that folder I had
is that like I mentioned something very
important Gregson it's natural doesn't
come because why shouldn't think it was
agony which So I guess the yes but the
effort he made ought to be shot to get out
of this match Botha just possible
he wanted someone to remember
him because. You may wish to call it to
someone who signed as someone who knew my
concept of time
a woman. Come
and. Talk to go to this team but having
said Mr Holmes ten minutes ago thank you.
That's
a bizarre properties John just bank. Book.
But remember don't tell this to me just
as you can kind of look into it one.
Glasses in the balance and catch
the ten thousand yesterday just as
a bet young woman was in that it does that
suggest you want to be paid up something
percent bad I still don't think sweet
blackmail you don't think he paid it out to
someone who saw him notice on the plane
when George never met anyone he didn't have
that woman's finger and the
empty did have a lot of
a lot of cash today finds out about that
now watching the game is afraid to fight
yesterday's no matter how
fault the accusation is made
a miss. Sometimes it's like throwing
a. Geologist going to see these mothers
seem to I rather think that nothing was any
one man come home not expected to leave the
whole organization going about killing
people and chopping off the thing is all
quite possible never heard of whoever is
behind all this think it's the out of his
mind and the country by definition it's
my assumptions are correct this little
scheme has some kind of the most brilliant
and ruthless intellect the world has ever
known you don't mean Professor Maria I do
the study Holmes you got him on the brain
which is the first time in as many months
he suspected him of that unsolved crimes.
And he is he's now yes he was hanged in
Montevideo well over
a year ago I hope that someone was hanged
at Montevideo under that name but I'll
stake my reputation the money obvious
a lie if I'm here now in London. And
I'll get the Dr Watson with me now
is Dr Watson thinking
no no I'm afraid I have
a touch of fact to them
oh that's well that's
a different thing and that's
because well that's what it.
Is it's about teachers not mood and then
I let them talk to try to get that.
Fact to get in the car was
news. Fourteen stone.
Fourteen stone so the person
that would like to serve up on
a stool to see because
there is so I want to be
a law against that people keep DICKIE BIRD
Well so little that I felt that I don't
use Thanks except what was let me know
what's in him that will. Elliptically tell.
Me What made you. Think.
Oh Professor My God outside which we're
getting credit is at the bottom and it's
a pleasure this is it Scotland Yard would
be interested it's very convenient to me
to have constant time to look at Montevideo
I never dreamed of phoning you thank
you the thought occurs to me Mr. That that
are some advantages of living within the
law and I think up to this extent.
And I get on in life
a little comforts me multum all
my bigger problem which is down
Thank you.
I'm not with this money I do what can I do
for you everything that I have to say it
was already cost John I'm my answers
now dot com shows that final
I do think I should not rest until you are
hanging for the thing that matters no
proof and I. Should.
Have you I could turn you over to the
police here and now you could if you did
you'd never see Dr Watson I'm going.
To telephone call. Iran's assumed you
had taken some such caution.
And I should have snatched up
a revolver and indulged in
a fit if your goods when you came
in not on you. Not smart enough.
To bend to spit you about any harm comes
to talk about too much will seek you out I
shall not rest until I find you and when
I do no harm will come to Dr Watson this
time and I can't answer for the future
stems I should strongly advise you to drop
skates silly thinking about it had many
encounters in the past you have to
place me on the gammas I tell you I
shall never stand again but if you were
instrumental in any way in bringing about
my destruction you will not be alive to
enjoy your satisfaction with a lock
together in the case which then is
a hand in hand with
a challenge that would make this wouldn't
it and I read it if I did with it.
And don't have to hang yourself I'm going
to more times than tell you I don't want
your filthy Hewlett's is only
a compass. He like to have not to put
in and let all my good man give you in
charge he would like to have you.
In the last resort I know it is
a pitcher in tomato status. Oh
I work in time and I'm. Just going
on to look for you know what for.
You don't think I know my way about but
you're right I don't bluff so practical
because in the world in. The wild goose
chase exactly doesn't number one cause me
lose some fools I do the
job. If you see anyone.
Anywhere in the old. System that was
a secular group that you know I left you
to some of the fact that the pickings
someone my dear Watson was perfect somebody
out himself that's just called on me
and you let him go I don't mind why well
he blessed me into believing that he was
holding
a friend of mine is hostage and he also
or nobody very important to that of
a man I believe medical
and I know I'm. A bit of
a lot of us who need. T.
Talk
a job to do away with. The set and
continue to save money I could
go because of me I don't try to. Lose
your love. When they know they don't care
about much. And we should never
Him we shall never hear.
I know the motive but I think about us
all I have to find out now is the method
used with the. Yes How does money out
to get them to the scene of the crime
how do you not think it's on them. And how
does he scanned them into believing that
. He may have committed those
atrocious letters I'm so
curious. Curious.
But because that's window in the it's
a house street. That's not front.
No not now I'll stake my life
on that So how does this. I.
Can go over outside or see the smell of
Christian can follow along comes the
world's going to put it like that is
wasted time think about shutting windows
decided I'd better take
a torch look at what. Signify just productive
talk to walk to the top of the muck
you proposed it was just
a couple Casper's read
a good book was very good idea very good
idea like a night watch when you have
a nice three but I have
a time. For
. Thinking about the house.
But still said.
Right right.
Except coupler reading
a book. You
can buy it does not cost you I found such
a second ago about
a little but do you see the incident you
may have noticed that that all through the
ages prominent names
have come to know it is.
The favorite terrible trouble again this
is not seen with the smashed battle of
Iraq you Corporal Williams
militates read this just in the Army is
a cancer that. They
perceive in all of us. It
seems that is the product that you
see these. So it is complex and it
was Stephan taking. Care of
a malaria. Slight. Why
did you try to kill me I
had to kill him I had to
snap out of this topic what
shamming. Who told you to kill me
she told me she don't know
she told me I couldn't miss
Well like you did miss you
murderer I know better but since.
She told you you had to do
it. I had to do it and I got
it right that method used in the think
about it is I don't want to just isn't my
D.S.
I know it's meant to them and it wasn't
against to that's the devilish thought of
it I think the man's that that those whose
job it was I that somebody are going to
think about us. I think
you'll find that you can
drink. Like you've got it all pass Mr
wrist watch the lighted
look like. I say go on for
size Let's get
a phone number. Williams
will give us an address
the God complex and so that anyone can get
it. WITNESS IN THE think about it and I
hope you're guessing right Mr
Holmes get up with him now
go with Inspector Griggs and
anybody tells you I'm on.
Going to come to terms of it if I
don't but not when I. Well you do
believe that PHILIP WILLIAMS The
sympathizers logistics of George Tenet was
hypnotized too I'm quite sure that Huckabee
thinks about how to do it why didn't
these people makes
a joke to the modem so. I
didn't want to get in hang. One
of the black men do you think the actual
murder is my gang and that particular
simple technique kill
a woman to say something like cut off the
fingers and if I understand the severed
finger is public to blackmail to come to
the minute. I'm sick of living in his
pocket and I got that you know I guess
you can die for all he knows he may have
committed the atrocious crime during time
but for lack of sanity that state will
establish them our law that made us take
a look at it and obviously you see it's
wet at this point in this image and being
human that the people think
anything other than stands on
a charge that will make you put in
a bullet. If you believe that the
only possible explanation you
think this is this is a woman with
a blonde left aside the woman who
invented I didn't invent the I saw.
You talking about that woman my idea was
to me was with the dog when he left and
because I saw how their eyes will see her
again and Williams will be people that's
why it's important to say
he will identify an.
Effective action. Against
every constable in
the district yes I'll be able to run what
happened Williams is missing Great Scott
. My question thank
you God going to do you think we have to
say. No to that because what we can to you
know think that MY GOD money I
think anything is possible.
When you. Say And I think it is possible.
Good morning to send somebody empty
your stocking I'm dressing another job.
This isn't. Is there anything wrong
with you'll see justice going to
not going to. Try one
comp because you can't.
Get it. I have the data from the.
Shock enough to split the head with those
toes away until they're needed to stand
up to their instruments but
the my way is an idiot and.
Really you should let me. Get
dressed Holmes and Watson just that
basis to my staff. Meeting take the
whole of the company to someone.
Else and one that is a suspect it's merely
a suspicion it's obvious that the see the
damage that I hope. Williams passed away
before I could talk for medical.
What you want me to do. My job.
And induce him to come back here.
Is not a bit dangerous it was
a meeting wish I could have just
attention today because I have
a you say you didn't see your face again
but. How just said it was given to
a couple you. Don't have so
much as one week you can stage
a book in the office and you're going
around saying you can lead him anyway. It's
up to you to take advantage of any
opportunity that man arises. This way please
don't go that. Kill the
throes of a thank you as
a matter of. Business this
is another mumbo jumbo I
was a medical man you must
listen to this place about
a boss that maybe ninety percent of the
tests the crux of the worst kind of thing
wrong a lot of self exploiting
morons. Are probably happy to make
a mistake and your brother Mycroft suggested
I might be able to heat up valued
member of AA groups of charlatans
and priests. And the good
news is my rant about the life one
does not exist in the midst of
a little experimental session if it's any
moment that you have to join us. I'm very
instructive for you thank you those who
are going to both the good and. The
safest if you think that
you. Feel it is conceded by
a new position especially as is value in
cases where the administration of local
law does allow that safety is in the advice
of the buzz but. For the sake of late
comers I may say that I have placed this
subject under profound hypnosis in this
condition you can feel no pain even under
applications which normally would be
excruciating. Excuses based contest
you having
a peaceful sleep feel nothing. And
your hands without sensation over
it along the
conjugate me all right.
As you would serve the needle has been
processed completely through the subjects
have no feeling no pay. This lack of
feeling is the one infallible test.
Found. For those who have
drugs. Definitely not.
God and wake up the well and rested
remember no paid anywhere wake up wake up
and say we're going to
begin all through. This
crisis. These only people who come
here don't know how to keep dropping
in all the time because it's all right
for those who believe because I'm
a professional man myself and you don't
believe in hypnotism doctor why. Certain
types of the stuff people money people
go on you think that's true but. With an
ounce of can. You see right through
this is going through right
through my desk right through.
Up with people who might say.
Excuse me to step over
here. Let me show you how
easily we shot up to them
and take advantage of now.
This is. One of those traction
on the people mind. The
continuous motion. They just get
themselves. Of course you could
stand it till doomsday to watch.
With no attempt to total. Might make you.
Drowsy like the why charisma of
road at night when you want Christ.
To. Broken. The road goes Kong na na
round and round always
the same winding line.
Grouchy tired left the
road can mean to you when.
Dom around. The school grounds. A road to.
Open your eyes then up.
Now Dr Watson you're on
a holiday in Scotland the country is
amazingly beautiful We're coming to
a street. That's
a take your shoes and socks off.
Like OK. That
will do I that make it waterproof
and I don't mind the pebbles.
Down.
When I tell you to let.
Nobody was allowed to.
I think your new. Hat.
I love this particular. One you're looking
for is to me to have taken you to take
money out of you to get washed out of the
winds but it's essential not going to
help me with money out in time in the
tank who's just my really struggling as I
just said to be dyed. I think I'm up to
testosterone Now I will tell it to the
gathering of serious students of
a great time and I find myself in the company
of the two. Men did today have their
brains with those men must for the truth
to make laugh of your childish crude ticks
I'm Sam in complete agreement with you
madam this is most unnecessary before I'm
stuck on zero bigger problems that
I need to go to like Oh that's
a service madam thank you. And I set up
crazy Robin about the situation but you see
Honestly to me is that you get someone to
Pakistan something coming that's we have
begun it's
a couple of them because I
should be denied good. Thank
you I didn't know there was such
a good but the last was just
back and again I thought
a little six effort was
good in the league so I had
a great thank you I thought I
did lose my head in the commitment.
But you see hypnotism is almost
a religion. I know so well I can do to
help you and I can benefit from trivial
because I know that
a little about it that's why I went to
them as much as we see another person does
not in the case I'm working on tell me
about and that's George Clooney and he was
he quite well known to go I thought I'd
come to see this last time I spoke to
George was going to come because.
He was sitting there and
I'd be putting his new table
together thanks to God it
was a charming little
bit it was a. Likeness
a good. Turning
to just say I was. Getting
up. Helen it's pricing
are made but I'm getting
a little older I should say.
Because God in my life I got
hold of the case is beyond me I can imaging
people of its. Apple if I could help it
. I should be grateful.
It is critical I go
back. To the design more than one
thing here. I'm not suggesting
that you think I can help
you if you can't. Get
a pleasant experience. The
life you think that all of you have to
access to health I'm afraid your rather
difficult. To have the help.
You carry medical. Drugs.
No I'd rather not if you don't mind as
a matter of fact I'm not myself but trying
to. Leave it the best means the good
stuff. Well as
a matter of fact I don't proof that it is.
Just that you wish you don't have to go
on with it. Wait a minute wait
a minute. All right something can
really quite come. Cannabis
to comics. In the world.
Because.
You feel yourself going down don't
try to get into. Because you
do what we can just picture I wonder why.
No one was empty our mind
of every other school
followed emotionally.
Through school and not only
one. Day.
Changes in. Other life.
Little specks of light
moon and.
Dressed.
Bend. And your bank of muttering of.
Your fund and. Give it one.
When your rest. Gentoo.
Here is. Stand up and.
Open your. Face this way
and. They're dealing with the
camera man maybe shamming
this just one man and I will
test it messes it up since.
That'll do doctor it couldn't
take insensibility it's
a knife I congratulate you
Lydia ten rounds to have
now walked the day of
the down. Ten right I tell you to write
I haven't lost the case Jack and I felt
I had outlived my usefulness That's all I
have to decide and my life
sign your name about it.
Oh that's.
But it won't look like. I'm.
The guy. That's.
Rolled. Out ten the last.
Load at the end of the tether.
Stop you must walk to the end you're now.
Lead to an open doorway you can pass trade
in perfect faith in the road to be on
the dull way you'll find what you've
been looking. At anticipating but i'm
time I'd gone.
Through the open doorway you will find
the man responsible for the thing.
And I'm quite enjoying it. Dispels.
Said to stand perfectly still.
Because I know what I'm doing.
Because seven and.
Probably doing. Kept. Out of trouble.
I substituted the drug
of my own for the one.
Although it leaves the subject conscious
renders them quite incensed and accounted
for my lack of reaction
to some. Impressive haul.
I was. Thank you.
I was going to settle. On the
gallows it's not been made.
I'm thinking of all the women who can come
and go in safety in the street and my
thighs keep watching the Heavens
and I don't like the way we to
a friend of privilege to watch over us.
All right here where.